

Jovita Morkūnė Quality Assurance Specialist

- +370 636 58227
- jovita.morkune@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/jovita-morkune/
- Kaunas, Lithuania

SUMMARY

I am responsible, diligent, attentive and have good interpersonal skills. I am used to an agile work environment and can quickly adapt to changing business requirements.

Over the past 5 years, I had an opportunity to work with culturally diverse teams, where I was focusing on ensuring a high level of quality in the work my team was doing.

Currently, I'm studying a lot to become a software QA engineer. I would love to join a software company where I could create value by contributing to the quality assurance of interesting software products while also gaining more practical experience.

EXPERIENCE

Sourcery Academy for Testers Student

Devbridge

07/2020 - Present

Quality Improvement Specialist

R1 RCM

03/2016 - 02/2020

- Conducted monthly process reviews for each team member per the quality assurance review procedures.
- Ensured the high-quality work of my team specialists.
- Investigated trends, analyzed root causes of rejected claims, and proposed solutions to resolve any concerns.
- · Prepared and leaded training of new and existing staff.
- Improved processes with macro commands to increase productivity and to avoid repetitive errors.
- · Initiated additional projects with other teams, which helped to generate more income for the company.

Account Resolution Specialist

05/2015 - 03/2016

Intermedix

- Identified reasons for denied insurance claims and effectively resolved them by determining a course of action in the revenue cycle management process.
- Made calls to insurance companies when needed.
- Maintained high productivity and work quality results.
- Worked on various projects, collaborated with team members to reach the team goals.

EDUCATION

International Business 2018

Kaunas University of Technology - Master's degree

Finance 2015

Kaunas University of Technology - Bachelor's degree

CERTIFICATES

End to End Testing with Cypress: CodeMash (Pluralsight)

04/2020 - Present

JavaScript Essential Training (LinkedIn)

04/2020 - Present

Learning SQL Programming (LinkedIn)				03/2020 - Present
End-to-End JavaScript Testing with Cypress.io (LinkedIn)				03/2020 - Present
Programming Foundations: Software Testing/QA (LinkedIn)				03/2020 - Present
The Web Developer Bootcamp (Udemy)				02/2020 - Present
Global Collaboration Certificate (X-Culture)				12/2017 - Present
SKILLS				
Teamwork	Expert	HTML/CSS	Beginner	
Quality Assurance	Advanced	MongoDB	Beginner	
Analytical Skills	Advanced	SQL	Beginner	
Time Management	Intermediate	Postman API	Beginner	
JIRA	Intermediate	Cypress	Beginner	
JavaScript	Beginner			

LANGUAGES

English Intermediate Lithuanian Native

Russian Basic